How is it that you Russian
Как так выходит что вот вы русские
guys die in the war and Akhmat, in short,
пацаны умираете на войне а Ахмат короче
gets a mega pile of money there They are all
получает Мега куча бабок там Они все
so equipped, they are sitting in Chechnya there are
такие экипированы сидят в Чечне там
tens of thousands of people He has, like, a
десятки тысяч человек у него типа да
pile Well, everyone has a license, he was just born,
куча Ба у каждого права только родился у
he already has a license, he has
него уже права есть
a car, he thinks that's all It's possible, it's sometimes annoying
тачка думает всё Можно иногда раздражает
That Russians are weak, sometimes they give in,
Что русские слабые иногда дают слабину
some [ __ ], they are afraid of bearded people Oh,
каких-то [__] боятся бородатых
great, soldier, great, let's have a normal
О здорово солда здорово давай нормально
conversation,
пообщаемся
let's I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky, Ukraine And where are
давай я из города Хмельницкий Украина А
you from? I'm from Crimea, it's cool, Tatar,
ты откуда я с Крыма прикольно татарин
Crimean, nothing Well, the Tatars all ran away,
Крымский ни о чём Ну татары все убежали
where did they run away to Where, where, where, far
куда они убежали та Куда куда куда
away, to their homeland,
подальше к себе туда на родину скорее
most likely And who are you, to what homeland do they have
всего А ты кто на какую родину у них
Crimea, Homeland Yes, what kind of Crimea is
Крым Родина Да какой там Крым там
left there, I don't know Well, I have
осталось не знаю Ну у меня есть там
panto Tatars there, Ade, the Tatars were mobilized
панто татари Аде ро татар мобилизовали
Well, where did they run to, see
Ну куда они убежали см
Bashkiria,
Башкирию
Bashkiria, the majority of Bashkiria, Bashkiria
Башкирию большинство Башкирию Башкирии
Tusya,
Туся
cool, I got it And you, mobile, Zro, a
прикольно понял А ты мобили Зро
contract soldier, not me, a contract soldier In short,
контрактник не я контрактник Я короче
how did I leave  to serve and it so happened that
как я ушёл служить и так получилось что
a mess began Well, so you went to serve as a
началась заваруха Ну так ты ушёл служить
contract soldier yes Yes, not me, ul, to serve on
контрактником да Да не я ул служить на
an urgent basis, as it were, but I wanted I wanted
срочку как бы но я хотел Я хотел саму
Odessa itself on a contract
одесс на контракт
So and ul, to serve, it so happened that
Вот и ул служить так получилось что
well, connected you, how much are you now then it
ну связал тебе сколько те сейчас тогда
turns out to be twenty
получается двадцатка с
plus
плюсом
Yes, who is so impudent there,
Да кто там такой дерзкий тебя
he lifted you up He opened the door, I understood And what are
поднял он Дверь открыл понял И что вы
you In short, how are you
Короче как тебе
serving that Well, how Do
служится та Ну как Домой
you want to go home and
хочется а ты где Что не дома
where are you That I'm not at home, no, I'm not at home, but where have I not been at home
не я не дома намал а где Я дома не был
For a year and 4 months, even a little more I do
Уже год и 4 месяца даже чуть больше Уже
n't remember exactly whether to close the door I'm
точно не помню дверь закрывать Я сейчас
going out now So where are you if you're not at home
выйду Так а где ты если не дома та Где
Where, where on the territory of Russia and you weren't thrown
где на территории России а вас не кинули
there Kursk To protect not in Kursk there are
там Курск Защищать не на Курске там
other teasers there are enough people Well,
другие подразни там хватает людей Ну
something is missing there, some problems
что-то не хватает там какие-то проблемы
I see I'm promoting yes, problems, statistics I
я смотрю продвигаю да проблемы стати Я
also looked there yes, he knows what kind of
тоже там смотрел да знает что там за
problems there are Let them do whatever they want
проблемы Пусть что хотят то делают
Listen, you tell me, how am I Civilian I don't
Слушай вот ты мне как я Гражданский Я не
understand how Ukraine is small Yes, with such a
понимаю как Украина маленькая Да с таким
small military potential, it could
маленьким военным потенциалом могла на
seize the Kursk region on the fly
пасе захватить курскую
how how how Yes, it seems to me
область как как как Да мне кажется
they did it on purpose  I mean on purpose
специально сделали В смысле специально
Well, they are rewriting history that like there is
Ну историю переписывают что типа опять
a mess in Kursk again, our people cleaned it up
там в Курске заваруха там наши почистили
there
там
and there are no specialties, like yeah, they
и н специальности типа да специально
missed it on purpose Well, how is this a
пропустил Ну как это
border that should have been protected by
граница которая должна была защищена чем
anything and there is enough of everything, they just
угодно быть и всего хватает просто
did it So they missed it, why did they
сделали Так что пропустили для чего это
do it honestly Well, I don’t really get into politics I even
сделали честно Ну я в политику особо Я
though I get into it a little but I don’t want to get into it, they
хоть и лезу немного но я в неё не хочу
did it on purpose to stir up
лезть сделали специально чтобы развести
history Well, war is history, granny,
историю Ну война - Это история бабки
granny,
бабки
people, granny,
Люд баб
what will happen again, they
что снова будет там курскую область
cleaned up the Kursk region, there were battles there for so
зачистили там были бои там на протяжении
much, so much Well, it seems to me like
там столько столько-то Ну мне кажется
that Well, people have different opinions, so Well,
так Ну у людей разное мнение поэтому Ну
wait, listen, with that logic, they can even
подожди слушай то с такой логики могут и
let troops in near Moscow so that, like,
под Москву подпустить войска чтобы как
history I don’t know what they’re up to there Well, I
историю Я не знаю что они там мутят ну я
really don’t understand at all, we
на самом деле вообще не понимаю у нас
just have troops, sometimes I even
просто войск я вот иногда даже ну
thought about it, we have so many troops sitting at the PDP, I
задумалась у нас ППД столько войск сидит
answer and they just sit For what
вот отвечаю и они просто сидят Для чего
Kakh, I don’t know They have their own kind of
Ках ж не знаю У них типа своя какая-то
tactics, you know, they just sit and
тактика вот просто зна мы просто сидят
rest there until 6, they work, go home,
отдыхают там до 6 отработали пошёл домой
there’s tea, coffee, there’s a disco, clubs A
там чай кофе там дискотека клубы А
guys there
пацаны там
well guys
ну пацанов
from maybe it turns out someone is sawing off money from them
от может получается кто-то на них бабки
like writing out that they are supposedly
пилит типа выписывает что они вроде как
in combat They are all there in the
на боевых Они там все В
rear kill yourself feel good
тылу уби себя хоро чувствуют
Moby guys who are sitting well not at the
Моби ребята которые сидят ну не на
front They get here loot there are in
фронте Они получают вот лутаю есть в
Crimea even uh get 200 plus Well that
Крыму даже э получают 200 с плюсом Ну то
is 300,000 loot drives a BMW
есть 300.000 лутает ездит на бэхе
scratches himself well F bosses also
чухается себя хорошо фе босы тоже хорошо
work well uh for civilians I
работают э у мирных граждан Я кстати
just found out by the way just in one word uh Well
только узнал просто одним словом ээ Ну
there is no human as they say everywhere ka No matter
людского как говорится нету везде ка
what kind of Ukrainian you are there there is an American
Каким бы ты там не был украинцем там
I have no human at the moment people
амери лю людского в моменте нету людей
start to get impudent for them just not enough at least
начинают наглеть им всего мало хотя бы
people They think shniks you mean F
люди Они думаю шники имеешь в виду ф
bosses yes Well yes like military police like
босы да Ну да типа военная полиция типа
FES and also twist there there give me a car
Фес и тоже там крутят там дай машину
I'll drive in the end there they take a car
погоняю в итоге там берут машину
bring bolts with there with well a couple of bolts
привозят болты с там с ну пару болтов
there and four wheels that's the maximum that
там и четыре колеса вот максимально что
they bring a car there at Well there is no human loot money
привозят тачку там у Ну людского нету
buy yourself Well, personally,
бабки лутает купите себе Вот ну лично я
I bought myself a car I won't even I did
я купил себе машину я даже не буду я её
n't buy it myself I bought it with the guys I need to
не сам купил Я купил её с ребятами надо
take it I take it and they do what they do they
отвез я отвожу а они как делают они
drive up there I'm there so loaded
подъезжают там я там такой заряженный у
I have a gun there now the guys will come out with
меня там ствол сейчас там ребята выйдут
a car Let me drive there for a couple of days
тачку Дайте там погонять на пару дней
they bring it That's not how it's done it's not human it's
привозят Так не делается это не людское
necessary War is always war but human Well
нужно Всегда война войной но людском Ну
you need to be human Let's start with that I also
людьми нужно быть начнём с того я ещё
saw such stories there a resident of the Kursk
видел такие истории там жителе Курской
region Donetsk wrote down that it
области Донецкой записывали что
turns out these shelves are swearing that they don't
получается вот эти полках мат что они не
fight but only rob the population taking
воюют а только грабят население забира
all sorts of things there I don't understand at all
там всякие дела Я вообще не понимаю
how Yes they are generally wild people I'm looking for Well
каким Да они вообще дикие люди я ище Ну
they Well I served with the guys Well they are wild
они Ну я служил с ребятами Ну они дикие
They take it from their own just
люди Они у своих же отбирают просто
comes there a guy bought Doshirak He
приходит там пацан Доширак купил Он
Listen bro I didn't make it to the store here I
Слышь братан я там магаз не успел сюда
gave the Doshirak and that's it the guys immediately silence
дошик отдал и всё пацаны сразу тишина
they are silent they took the Doshiraks there let's have
молчат они там дошики забрали пошли
fun or the guys are watching TV they
кайфа или там ребята телик смотрят они
fly in we'll watch boxing guys
залетают мы бокс будем смотреть пацаны
with whom they immediately went Well, these are not
сразу с ком походили Вот нуно это не
people I don’t know how they were even
люди я не знаю как их вообще сюда
let in here it turns out yes Well, how does it
запустили получается да Ну как так
happen that you Russian guys
выходит что вот вы русские пацаны
die in the war and Akhmat, in short,
умираете на войне а Ахмат короче
gets a mega pile of money there They are all
получает Мега куча бабок там Они все
so equipped they sit in Chechnya there are
такие экипированы сидят в Чечне там
tens of thousands of people he has like a
десятки тысяч человек у него типа да
pile Ba each has a license he was just born
куча Ба у каждого права только родился у
he already has a license he
него уже права есть
thinks everything is possible Yes, these are just
тачка думает всё можно Да это просто
Russians that’s why it just sometimes
русские вот меня просто иногда
irritates me
раздражает
Russians are weak sometimes they give in to
русски слабые иногда дают слабину
some kind of slack they are afraid of
каких-то боятся
bearded ones if he had hooked me or
бородатых если бы он мене зацепил или
my family or done something
мою семью или так сделал поступок
ugly I would have been for him And let him
некрасивый я бы его за И пусть бы
come there Regiment Regiment honestly a full
приехала там Полк Полк честно полный там
regiment there And what Well, there are guys who are
полк И что Ну не есть ребята которые
adequate I’m not speaking for everyone there are
адекватные Я не говорю за всех есть
really adequate ones here we have guys
реально адекватные вот у нас есть ребята
who are from Dagestan from Grozny very
которые там с Дагестана с Грозного очень
adequate people with whom you can
адекватные люди с которыми можно
communicate and there are Well, these are people We also
общаться а есть Ну это люди У нас тоже
have such people well I would like to there
есть такие люди это ну как бы я хочу там
there well I didn’t really serve with them but I know there
там ну я с ними особо не служил но знаю
is humanity in them But in many there is no
есть людское в них Но в многих нет
humanity in many there is no  people As they say,
людского в многих нет люди Как говорится
there are good people, there are bad people, and no matter what
есть люди хорошие есть плохие и Каким бы
nationality you are,
ты не был национальностью
so how is it that
поэтому Ну а как так получается что вот
Ramzan Kadyrov doesn't have this human, but
у Рамзана Кадырова нет этого людского но
in short, they give him money and his guys, like,
ему короче дают бабки и его пацаны типа
don't die at all. I have a question, are you
вообще не умираю Вот у меня вопрос ты
writing it down somewhere, no, I'm
записываешь куда-то это нет так
communicating, I need to write it down, I can write it down on my phone now.
общаюсь надо записать могу сейчас на
No, it's not just that many questions, you never know, you
Да не просто много вопросов ты мало ли
write them down there, then God forbid, I'm
там записываешь потом не дай Бог там я
not there, look. Why are there questions? I'm a simple
не я смотри Почему вопросы я простой
person, I'm always interested. I
человек мне всегда интересно я раз в
go to Roulette once a week, I talk to people,
неделю выхожу в Рулетку общаюсь с людьми
and if the military tries, it's
и если попытается военными с военными
just interesting to talk to the military because
как раз интересно поговорить потому что
you know. I don't understand at all. I watch
вы шарите я я вообще не понимаю я смотрю
videos on Telegram, "flew in, flew in,
в телеграме ролики прилетела прилетела
died, died." I don't understand this whole
умер погиб Я не понимаю этой всей типа
kitchen. I was just talking to a girl from
кухни Я просто общался с девчонкой с
Novosibirsk. Her boyfriend died, and she
Новосибирска У неё парень погиб и она
says. That's why I thought about it. She
говорит Вот почему я задумался Она
said that they let her boyfriend in, in short,
сказала что её парня пустили короче там
where this regiment of Akhmat was supposed to be
где вот этот полко Ахмат должен был
stationed in the Kursk region, they let the guy in, a
стоять в Курской области пустили парень
conscript, conscripts were thrown in, and in general,
срочник срочников кинули и в общем они
most of them surrendered, some died, like  And
большинство сдались часть погибла типа А
Akhmat left, like, I heard something like that too,
Ахмат ушёл типа я что-то я это тоже
at first, at first, like, Akhmat
слышал поначалу поначалу что типа Ахмат
left there, I wasn't honestly, I won't
там отошёл я не был честно я не буду
say how it was, but I wasn't there,
говорить как оно было но я там не был
many said, like, I have
многие говорили да что типа у меня есть
a boy, that's where I live, Well, my brother,
пацанчик вот где я живу Ну у моего брата
that's his Kent, he served, Well, more precisely,
это его Кент он Служил Ну точнее учился
he studied together at school, he went to serve in the military,
вместе в школе он пошёл служить срочную
he was sent to Kursk, that is, to the
службу его отправили на Курск то есть на
border, why were conscripts sent there,
границу зачем туда срочников отправляли
I don't know, so I'm answering, I'm a military man, I
Я не знаю вот отвечаю ть я и военный Я
don't know the Kursk region at all, I
вообще я курскую область не знаю Я там
wasn't there, and I won't, so let's start with that,
не был Туту и не буду вот начнём с того
I don't want to go there, Well, there's
вот я туда не хочу ехать Вот ну там
a meat grinder there, in fact, that's it, I'm
мясорубка на самом-то деле вот Мне здесь
fine here, that's how they say, Where we are
хорошо хорошо Как говорится Там где нас
not, that's how he was on the border, too, he
нет вот так вот он был на границе тоже
defended them, they paid him medals, the women there,
защищал ему там медали баб выплатили вот
Well, thank God, he stayed alive, everything came there,
Ну слава Богу жив остался всё пришёл там
too, he told how it really was,
тоже рассказал как оно было на самом
he didn't say that, like, they ran away, Well,
деле он не говорил что типа там убежали
like, most of the conscripts there
Ну вообще типа большинство там срочников
were, I know that they were, Yes, they
было это я знаю что они Да они
fought back, Well, what can a conscript do for a year,
отбивались Ну а что срочник может год
What is a year?  boy in short in general
Что такое год пацан короче вообще Ему
it's like this boy came from civilian life they
оно так пацан пришёл с гражданки ему
gave him a gun they just put his uniform on him and he
дали ствол просто одели его форму и он
stands there thinking that the gate is attacking us
стоит думает та ворот на нас нападают
guys who are trained who are older
ребята которые обучены которые постарше
there are armored vehicles there are tanks what
идёт там бронетехника идут танки что он
can he do
может сделать
Yes many many surrendered I'm not him
Да многие многие в плен сдались я не он
maybe at the training ground only shot a couple of times that
може на полигоне пару раз только стрелял
conscript you know and that's not a fact yes
тот срочник знаешь и то не факт да может
maybe he just came and got
быть он вообще только пришёл и попал
there that's why Well the stories are different As they
туда поэтому Ну истории разные Как
say Well well I don't understand either
говорится Ну ну я тоже я не понимаю я
at first when I was watching this news Yes
сначала когда вот это смотрел новости Да
I thought that some fakes e conscripts on the
я думал что какие-то фейки е срочники на
border I think well it can't be how
границе я думаю ну не может быть как это
could they put children like guarding the
могли поставить детей типа охранять
border during a war well this is
границу во время войны ну это ж прикол
some kind of joke this is the First Line the half
какой-то бред Это ж Первая линия полу
was also in shock in fact very
тоже был в шоке на самом-то деле очень
Yes well damn here I don't understand either I
Да такое Да ну блин тут тоже не понят Я
just when it turns out in August
просто это же когда получается в августе
somewhere around the month Yes that it went into the Kursk region of
где-то месяц Да что в курскую область
Ukraine at first it seemed to me that
Украины зашла мне сначала казалось что
these were also fakes that this fake was specially
это тоже фейки что это фейк специально
dispersed Well I also I just don't remember
разгоняют Ну я тоже я как раз не помню
somewhere a hospital  I was lying down reading
где-то госпиталь лежал тоже читал эту
all this crap too, what about lying in the hospital What
всю фигню ти а что в госпитале лежал Что
happened, I don't have anything
случилось та у меня нет там ничего
like that there was nothing serious I just had a rest Yes, I
такого не было серьёзно отлел просто Да
just decided to lie down there was something like here
просто полежать решил было такое тут
now you won't meet anyone, someone is wounded,
сейчас кого не встретишь кто-то раненный
someone died, like in general, war takes
у кого-то кто-то погиб типа вообще война
so many people, damn, yes, war
столько забирает людей капец да война
has taken a lot, to be honest So sit down
много забрало если честно Так посидеть
Here you are as military As you can see, because for
Вот вы как военные Как вы видите потому
example, I cannot understand from the point of
что я например не могу понять ни с точки
view of Ukraine or from the point of view of Russia
зрения Украины ни с точки зрения России
how this war should end Yes,
как это война должна закончиться Да вот
you military, what do you think, like what
вы военные как считаете типа ну что
should be a victory And do you think
должно быть победой А ты думаешь у нас у
we have a lot of information I'm
нас есть много информации Я на самом
actually cornered, let's start with that I'm
деле загнанный в угол начнём с того я же
telling you Elementary that well, well, I
тебе говорю Элементарно то что ну я не
can't go on vacation for 3 months Well, this is
могу сходить в отпуск 3 месяца Ну это на
actually wild on my part to
самом-то деле дико с моей стороны год 3
not be home for a year and 3 months Well,
месяца не быть дома
this is on No, well, it happens Yes, at the moment,
ну это это на Не ну бывает да моменте
someone hasn't been there for two, someone hasn't been there for three,
там кто-то уже два не был кто-то три не
as it were, and I understand them what it is I
был как бы и я их понимаю что это такое
want to go home I want to
хочется домой хочется к семье хочется
see my family I don't know my grandmother there I don't
увидеть там не знаю бабушку маму там не
know when was the last time there
знаю когда последний раз там
relatives die Yes yes I have a
родственники умирают Да да у меня вот
brother there well I have brothers there from
брат там ну у меня вот братья там с
Kharkov mother from Ukraine and like this
Харькова мама с Украины и как бы этот
Mom it is clear that she accepted that Well
Мама понятно что она приняла что Ну так
it happened it is clear that Mom well Mom
так случилось понятно что мама ну мама
is Mom she will accept what Well no matter what
есть мама она примет какой Ну с какой бы
side you are from Well in principle
ты там стороны не был вот Ну в принципе
and I am like well I do not want I am in this country I am
и я типа ну я не хочу я в этой стране Я
in this country everything is like well I am a patriot from
в этой стране всё типа ну я патриот с
my country let's start with that and somehow se s u
своей страны начнём с того и как-то се с
po you it turns out you your mom is
у по ты получается ты у тебя мама родом
from Ukraine Yes yes my mom is from Kharkov
с Украины Да да у меня мама с с Харькова
I have brothers from Kharkov who
у меня братья с Харькова которые там
wrote to my mom there that like we will come to
писали моей маме что типа мы придём в
Crimea you will sit in basements Well how is
Крым вы будете сидеть в подвалах Ну как
that they came you were a
это так они приезжали ты ж был
citizen of Ukraine and then in 2014 they
гражданином Украины это потом в 14м году
rewrote you of course Of course I am very
тебя переписали конечно Конечно я дуже
good Roma in Ukrainian mo So what are
гарно ромов на украинской мо Так а что
you well you are saying I am a patriot of this country
ты ну ты говоришь Я патриот этой страны
You were a patriot of Ukraine and they
Ты же был патриотом Украины и тебя
just rewrote you not Well I was I was
переписали просто не Ну я был я был
a kid what am I I never shouted Glory to
малой какой я я никогда не кричал Слава
Ukraine I even I was a kid there yeah Well
Украине Я даже я был малой там да Ну всё
anyway  you were born in Ukraine Yes you were a
равно ты ты родился в Украине Да ты был
citizen of Ukraine Now you were
гражданином Украине Теперь тебя
re-registered in Russia and you went to fight
переписали в Россию и ты пошёл воевать
for
за
Russia Yes that's exactly how it turns out you
Россию да именно так получается ты
betrayed your country Ukraine Well why
предал свою страну Украину Да ну почему
why Preda No no I didn't betray Ron I
почему Преда Да не я не предался рону я
Well I always considered myself Russian I
Ну я я себя считал всегда русским Я
never said look you could
никогда не говорил вот смотри ты мог
be
быть
ru e once you could be Russian Well you were a
ру е раз мог быть русским Ну ты был
citizen of Ukraine in Ukraine there are different
гражданином Украины в Украине же разные
nationalities Russians Belarusians live
национальности русские белорусские живут
all sorts you were not My dad is from the Omsk
всякие ты был вот не У меня папа Омской
region therefore Well my grandmother is from the Omsk
области поэтому Ну бабушка Омской
region I think Seya has Russian roots all the
области Я считаю Сея русски корни всё
time the roots are straight the surname is Russian there's
пор корни прям фамилия русская даже
nothing to even cling to it's cool I understood that
цепляться не за что прикольно понял то
is it from your dad I got it from my dad
есть это от папы у тебя У меня от папы
Yes he served in the SOM region
Да он сомс области
wanted to live the service there so with Uch
служил хоте прожить службу там так с Уч
that he met my mother at sea went
что с мамой встретился в море ходил
sailor Therefore I consider myself completely Russian on my dad's
моряк Поэтому я считаю себя по папиной
side My surname my
линии полностью русский У меня фамилия
surname is completely Russian from the
фамилия у меня русская полностью от
word not at all Even didn't want, for
слова совсем нету Даже а не хотел
example, to leave Crimea for my
например ну уехать с Крыма на родину
father's homeland on never never Never  I will
отца на никогда никогда Никогда не
leave Crimea I will stand to the last
покину Крым буду до последнего стоять
please Well don't mean it Well this is
пож Ну не имей в виду ну это ж Родина
your father's homeland Here are your ancestral lands No matter
твоего отца вот твои родовые земли
how many bullets you fired at me but
Сколько вы патронов во меня не зашло но
I will always stand for Crimea Crimea Crimea
я всегда буду стоять за Крым Крым Крым
Crimea is Crimeans this is a separate re
Крым - это крымчан это отдельная ре вот
your father is from Omsk Yes
у тебя отец родом из Омска Да там ещё
Kolchak once fought there Well well of
Колчак когда-то воевал Да ну то есть
course Omsk is a great place there Omsk people are
конечно великие места омские вот там
famous all over the world like that's
омичи известные на весь мир типа вот
why don't you go live in Omsk to
почему ты не поедешь жить в Омске
develop Omsk this is your homeland pre not
развивать Омск это родина твоих пре не
Why Why does grandma say like
Почему Почему бабушка говорит типа ну
well now the war will end there will be
вот сейчас там война закончится будет
time there they wanted to
время там меня там хотели сейчас недавно
transfer me to Omsk recently to the border guards there
в Омск перекинуть там пограничникам вот
I have an uncle from Omsk he has served the border guards all his
у меня дядя с Омска он пограничникам всю
life wanted to transfer me Well I would like to give
жизнь служит хотел меня перекинуть ну я
them up I
как бы ну я как бы их
don't feel like leaving I have guys here I would be
отда не чу уходить у меня тут ребята бы
fine here as they say Well fine
мне хорошо здесь как говори Ну хорошо
Where we are not there well I
Там где нас нет там ну я
Explain to me I don't know such a
лись Объясни мне вот я вот не шарю такую
thing Kherson how did it happen that Russia
штуку Херсон как получилось что Россия
gave Kherson I didn't believe that Ukraine
отдала Херсон я я не верил что Украина
Maybe to win back this was some kind of
Может отвоевать это вообще какая-то
fantasy Russia just took and
фантастика была Россия просто взяла и
ran away this is a fake Armed Forces you understand
убежала это ВС наиграно ты понимаешь
I have no anger If to me what Well
у меня злости нет Если ко мне че Хорошо
I am good to him it
я к нему
turns out well in Crimea they made a
хорошо получается в Крыму сделали
referendum and in Kherson they made the ref
референдум и в Херсоне сделали реф
thin
тоненькими
yes they also made a referendum Yes they declared it
да сделали тоже референдум Да объявили
part of Russia and then Putin took and
частью России а потом Путин взял и
said like to leave Kherson but imagine Well
сказал типа уйти из Херсона а прикинь Ну
and maybe it will be that
и может быть такое что также из Крыма
Russian troops will also leave Crimea As from Kherson
российские войска уйдут Как из Херсона
not from Crimea no one is unlikely anyone Well
не с Крыма никто навряд ли кто-то Да ну
it's far away a
это далеко
hundred so many defenses to go through we already have all the
сто столько оборон пройти у нас уже вс
lines there is something Trump will agree with
лини там что-то Трамп договорится с
Putin Yes they will give Crimea back to Ukraine the
Путиным Да отдадут назад Крым Украине
maximum maybe Trump will
макси максимум может что Трамп
agree this is a freeze all this is the
договорится это заморозка всё это
maximum No well who knows look for
максимально Не ну кто его знает смотри
example I will exchange the Kursk region for
например обменяю курскую область на
Crimea I am honestly such a person I would be ready
Крым Я честно такой человек я бы готов
if a pack would stand next to me I would be
если бы со мной стая бы стала рядом я
ready America just Which way would
готов был бы Америку просто Каким бы
it be from sapat to yourself all two Russians two
это от сапать себе всё два русских два
Slavic peoples they are laughing now
славянских народа они сейчас смеются
sitting there he wants to do something two
сидят там он что-то хочет сделать два
Slavic  he scolded the people there now
славянских народа он там сейчас поругал
They are fighting people there at the moment there are
Они воюют люди там в моменте там вот
swastikas there I tell him he has a
свастики там я ему говорю у него
T-shirt with a swastika there Okay there is
футболка там со свастикой Ну ладно там
this Ukrainian Tricolor Okay there are no words a
этот Триколор украинский Ладно слов нет
patriot of his country well when you have
патриот своей страны ну когда на тебе
swastikas just stop stop I
свасти просто стоп стоп я правильно тея
heard correctly that America is killing two
услышал что Америка убивает два
Slavic peoples Well and Russia is not a
славянских народа Ну а Россия не
Slavic people Ukraine is not a Slav so wait
славянский народ Укра не свя так подожди
So I see that Russia is killing two
Так я вижу что Россия убивает сейчас два
Slavic peoples now both Russians and Ukrainians
славянских народа и русских и украинцев
and America will lose its hands America is rubbing its
а Америка потеряет руки Америка потирает
hands but they did it they
руки но они ж этим они это сделали они
gave it to them So why I just can't understand
чку дали Так зачем просто не могу понять
Look I don't understand politics it's just
Смотри я в политике не разбираюсь просто
that you are more of a military man you are
да ты больше военный ты как бы к
closer to politics why then Putin started
политике ближе зачем тогда Путин начал
attacking so that Slavs would kill Slavs I can't
напал чтобы убивали славяне словян не
understand Honestly from my
понять Вот честно с моей ны
point of view it was earlier since a year they were
во конт это было ранее с года они там
bombing LNR DNR shouting that it was Russia and
бомбили лнр ДНР кричали что это Россия и
so on Why is Givi he himself Givi is from
так далее Почему Гиви он сам Гиви же с
Ukraine why did he fight for the NR DN he
Украины почему он воевал за НР дн он там
was there to the last held out because  he
был до последнего держался потому что он
understood that it was Ukraine that was bombing, taking out
понимал что это Украина бомбит вывозила
these ears of theirs, Bombing the children, they just did
эти з ушки свои Бомбила дети просто де
n't like that I left for
не понравилось что я на ком ушёл в
Russia on whom they had already started, you know something about
Россию они начали уже ка то ты шаришь в
politics, you would have said I don't understand,
политике бы ты говорил Я не разбираюсь
they started pumping Moscow on the gallows, there my
они начали качать Моск на гиляку там мои
brothers started writing to my relatives that
же братья начали писать моей родне что
we, we would come to Crimea, that the people themselves
мы мы придём в Крым что люди сами
wanted it, the people themselves wanted it, the people
захотели люди сами люди захотели люди
wanted it, they wanted it, they knew Your brothers from
захотели им зна Твои братья из
Kharkov from Kharkov Yes, they wrote to my
Харькова с Харькова Да они писали моей
mother that they would come to Crimea, in short, that we
маме что они придут в Крым короче что мы
would sit in basements Although they
будем сидеть в подвалах Хотя они
came home, Their grandmothers live there now, it
приезжали домой У них там бабушки сейчас
was necessary, as if the conflict were not
живут нужно было как бы конфликт бы не
in Kharkov, it turns out, They were
на Харькова получается Они что
Banderovites from Kharkov, they were from
бандеровцы из Харькова были они с
Kharkov It turns out they left They
Харькова Получается они уехали Они
came in the fourteenth year, they
Приезжали в четырнадцатом году они
came to their grandmother, they have relatives
приезжали к своей бабушки у них родня
living with us in Crimea, they came, it
живёт у нас в Крыму они приезжали
turns out, Mom is there, their mom's sisters are their
получается Мама там ихней маме сёстры
own, they came We communicated well with them
родные они приезжали Мы с ними хорошо
there Well, I was still little, porno I remember everything
там Ну ещё я малой был проно Я всё помню
as if in a picture  how they lived there under Ukraine,
как как на картинке как при Украине жили
here I am, back and forth from the stove, I
там вот я это с печка туда-сюда я это
remember all this We communicated well, they left, a
всё помню Мы хорошо общались они уехали
political conflict began, here Ukraine with
политический конфликт вот Украина с
Russia and they write to my mother, I didn’t
Россией и они пишут моей маме я ж не
write to him, I didn’t write to him that I would
писал ему Я же ему не писал что я сейчас
come there now, and they write text messages to my mother,
приду там и они пишут моей маме эсэмэски
here on Odnoklassniki, we will come to Crimea, you
вот в Одноклассниках мы придём в Крым вы
will sit in basements, you say, we will kill you
будете Сить в подвалах вы типа мы вас
all, there will
всех
be
поубивают быть
aggression, and what happened to them, that the Banderites
агрессия А что с ними их что бандеровцы
recruited them with God,
завербовали сбогом
he dresses me, I ask him, why did you
он одевает я ему вопрос Зачем ты её
dress her, I understand correctly, wait, your brother
одел Я прави понимаю Подожди твой брат
somehow became a Banderite one day, or
как-то в один день стал бандеро там или
something, I can’t
что не могу
understand, well, somehow it works out,
понять Ну как-то получается
yes, I mean, how did someone press a button
да В смысле как это кто-то нажал кнопку
and his brains became like someone
и у него мозги сталида ктото как будто
pressed a button and gave him some kind of
нажал ему кнопку дал какой-то какую-то
pill or something, well, from my side and
ему таблетку что ли Вот с моей стороны и
he,
он
I’m right, I understand correctly that
я правильно я правильно понимаю что
somewhere after Russia entered
где-то после того как Россия зашла в
Crimea, e, your brothers in Kharkov became
Крым э Твои братья в Харькове стали
Banderites, yes, well, yes, they started writing
бандеровцами да Ну да они начали писать
like that, and at the same time, they started writing  and now
так При этом они начали писать а сейчас
they are having fun in Poland they don't need it
они в Польше кайфуют им это не надо
at all they And look here is another
вообще они А смотри ещё ещё такой вот
interesting question it turns out yes
интересный вопрос получается да
uh after all America uh if now for 3
ээ всё-таки Америка ээ если сейчас 3
years we see yes because Putin
года мы видим да из-за того что Путин
attacked Ukraine Slavs are killing Slavs
напал на Украину славяне убивают славян
then maybe Putin didn't have to
то может быть Путину не надо было
attack it was necessary to
нападать нужно было дипломатическим
seek diplomatic ways to somehow come to an agreement and not if
искать как-то договориться а не если
Putin hadn't attacked Ukraine would have attacked
Путин бы не нападал бы Украина бы напала
If it could have waited if Ukraine
Если бы так может подождать если Украина
Napa had waited there was no time to wait it
Напа ждать не было времени ждать нужно
was necessary to act So why look everything
было действовать Так почему смотри всё
was recorded anyway the FSB is
было зафиксировано по-любому же ФСБ
working everything was
работает всё было
recorded Who has what boundaries look so
зафиксировал Кому какие грани смотри так
look if Ukraine had attacked the whole
бы смотри если бы Украина напала весь
world would have seen that it had attacked and that's it Russia would have
мир бы увидел что напала и всё Россия бы
demolished Ukraine no one even helped
снесла Украину никто даже не помог
Ukraine no one Russia doesn't have tactics
Украине никто У России нет тактики
to demolish if if Russia had to
сносить если если б надо было у России
demolish they would have demolished And listen and
сносить они бы сносили А слушай а
wait So you want to say that
подожди То есть ты хочешь сказать что
Ukraine was preparing to attack Russia so
Украина готовилась напасть на Россию так
yes of course they were preparing they
да конечно они готовились они постоянно
were constantly training they were driving their
у них были тренировки они подгоняй свои
troops closer the borders closer all this is through
войска границы ближе ближе это всё через
Well how is this ro question question question You
Ну как это ро вопрос вопрос вопрос Ты
as a military man I just don't know anything about it I'm in
как военный Я просто не шарю в этом я в
these matters I only played the computer game
этих делах Я только в компьютерную игру
Counter Strike how could Ukraine with the
в Counter срак играл как Украина с теми
troops it had in the second
войсками которая у неё была в д втором
year attack Russia at all where
году могла вообще напасть на Россию куда
could it
она могла
attack Well, how where did they have
напасть Да ну как куда у них у них было
something in their heads well it's not clear they already
уже что-то в голове ну непонятно они уже
wanted to attack in their heads and what did they
хотели нападать на голове а чем чем чем
attack with yes what was not there like this now
напала да чем что не было как это сейчас
I'm fighting there are supplies there are
же воюю техника есть поставки есть
now yes NATO has already pumped up the Mercedes
сейчас да НАТО уже накачала там мерсы
F16 there so they initially pumped up they were in
F16 так они изначально качали они в
Crimea so you understand in Crimea earlier in
Крыму чтоб ты понимал в Крыму раньше в
Evpatoria the city of Evpatoria in a part in a
евпатори города евпатори в части в
huge part maybe Well I don't know there on the
огромной части может Ну не знаю там по
map what part of the Americans
карте по какая там часть амери там
wanted to conduct
хотели проводить Ну
training there Well who are they
тренировки кто они такие
when so when everything let's not talk about
когда так когда всё давай не будем о
politics no no I just I just can't
политике не не я просто я просто не могу
understand
понять
how I have Boshe Assi on America that's from the
как у меня Боше Асси на Америку вот от
word completely I just want I would if I were
слово совсем Просто я хочу я бы будь я
such a person I would shoot Zhirinovsky
таким человеком я стрел Жириновский
spoke the truth America will not be it
правду говорил Америки не будет её
just it has already washed it once it will wash it once more
просто её уже умыла разок её ует ещё
and God willing that it will wash it Well
разок и даст Бог чтобы её умыла Хорошо
then everything is fine  conflicts I hope they get into
тогда все конфликты надеюсь они влазят
everything and people don't notice it they
везде и люди этого не замечают они
think don't
думают не
Hang out already supplies everything is fine just
Зависай уже поставляет всё хорошо просто
Well how does it turn out It seems to me that
Ну как Получается Мне кажется что
America is doing its own
Америка она себе занимается своими
thing there it creates computers the Internet
делами там создаёт компьютеры интернет в
launches into space and Russia turns out to be at
космос запускает а Россия получается
war with Georgia at war with Moldova at war with
воюет с Грузией воюет с Молдовой воюет с
Ukraine at war with everyone
Украиной со всеми
so these clashes America
воюет так эти стычки Америка и дат
provokes it It's just that it's everywhere Yes everyone
провоцирует Просто она везде онат Да все
says this all the military say that it
это говорят все военные говорят что она
gets into everything only we can't we
это влазит только мы не можем мы не
can't just take it without an order and just well
можем просто без команды взять и просто
honestly no matter how it sounds since its
ну честно как бы это не звучало раз её
honestly ho here's what for example if
честно хо вот что например если бы
an order came to do this to America how would you
пришла команда так ть Америку как бы вы
do it how would we do it yes yes
сделали как бы мы это сделали да да
just even well if you directly kill
просто даже ну если прямо убивать
America from the word completely then I think well
Америку от слова совсем то я думаю ну
Tem would have enough yes a couple of pieces of hazelnuts a
Тём хватило бы да орешника пару штук
piece four yes two hazelnuts I
штуки четыре бы да орешника два
think two hazelnuts would have been enough two
думаю два орешника бы хватило два
hazelnuts and there would be no America No well how is
орешника и не было бы Америки Да не ну
that well I'm not saying that it wouldn't have happened
как это ну я не говорю что бы не было
Just bring them into a conflict where it
Просто вывести их на конфликт откуда
came from they are in shock They were those
прилетело они в шоке Они же там эти
flying there they were  there they were in shock
летали они там в шоке были стреляли
they were just shooting they they They don't know how to fight
просто они они Они не умеют воевать
Well they're afraid
они Ну они боятся Честное
Honestly among
слово сре
them there on the satellite or whatever was flying and
них там спутнике или что летало да
scared they were running there Hey there
перепуганные там бегали Ау там
two hazelnuts were shooting they were just
стрелять два орешника они его просто
shouting it from Where did it come from from Russia
кричали это откуда Откуда это с России
baby Russia Listen and by the way
погнала детка Россия Слушай а кстати
about the hazelnut Where is this
насчёт орешника А где вообще этот
hazelnut Everyone was shouting So hazelnut hazelnut
орешник Все кричали Так орешник орешник
where is it no well it's there once Well they checked it
где он не ну он же там раз Ну они его
like how
как как
they checked
они проверили
Yegor Tile They said everything hazelnut And no
Егора Тиле Сказали всё орешника И больше
one has seen it anywhere else Well there won't be any more
его нигде никто не видел не Ну больше не
why they launched looked
будет по что они запустили посмотрели
how big is the radius of destruction how is it how is
сколько там радиус поражения как он как
it in general how is it Well how is it
он вообще как он Ну как он себя
feeling of course of course they
чувствует конечно конечно поло
felt that Why does
почувствовали что Почему Россия больше
n't Russia use the hazelnuts anymore And why kill
не использует орешник А для чего убивать
civilians so not peaceful for the military
мирных граждан так не мирных по военным
Let it be for military facilities for the hazelnuts
Пусть по военным объектам за орешника ли
Yes No why why should we release a new one
Да Нет зачем зачем нам новое выпускать
if we have the old one Wait Stop Here is
если у нас есть старое Подожди Стоп Вот
this hazelnut which the midam is the first time
этот орешник который первый раз
and where did they throw it when it
мидам а куда его кинули когда он
arrived
прилетел
hazelnut in the Dnieper
орешник в Днепр
right  Dnepr why
же Днепр поему
day Why won't they let another hazelnut tree
дне Почему другой орешник не пустят тоже
through such objects too So I'm saying why
по таким объектом Так я же говорю зачем
spend why spend new old
тратить зачем тратить новое старое
promotion there is its No why now
продвижение же есть его Не зачем сейчас
well why waste it Look I don't understand
ну зачем его тратить Смотри я не понимаю
one thing Why Russia only loses its
одного Зачем Россия лько теряет своих
fighters
бойцов
if it would have smashed all
если бы она бы этим реком разбила Все
Ukrainian military units with this river and that's all yes
воинские части украинские да и всё да
no yes no military units Well this is
нет да нет воинских частей Ну тут дело
not the point they are trying they are trying to
не в этом они стараются они стараются же
be closer to civilians in order to
быть ближе к мирным гражданам чтобы
then cause panic fuss political
потом навести панику суету политический
conflict that here Russian military are
конфликт что вот военные российские
killing civilians here is a video
убивают мирных граждан вот видео
Elementary recently a
Элементарно недавно было прилетела
cassette arrived How sorry I am for people Honestly
кассет Как мне жаль людей Честное слово
I even want to cry I just like a bang an old
аж плакать хочется я тако челок просто
lady was walking home with bread
шла бабушка домой с хлебом
where would this cassette arrived an old lady was walking
где это бы касет прилетела бабушка шла
there in what city
там в каком это городе
was this an old lady was walking home with
было бабушка шла там домой с
bread
хлебом
Kado see what city
Кадо посмотреть каком это городе
it is where it was you know not in Belgorod
это где это было знаешь не в Белгороде
not in Belgorod it was I don't know honestly
не не в Белгороде было не знаю честно
we need to
надо
see first
посмотреть первы
how the military was such a zone was tracked
ка военны было зону такую отследили
apparently and he got there just how can I
видимо и он попал просто его бы как это
say just looked how he
сказать просто посмотрели как он
works
работает
how  I got it right This first hazelnut tree was
как правильно понял Этот первый орешник
not for people or for the military but they just
не по людям не по военным а просто
let it go somewhere in a wasteland it just was
где-то в пустырь пустили он просто был
it was just like
он просто как бы
this as it is
этот как вот есть
in short it
короче
is called why
называется поему
it flies out on its own it has such a
вылетает он сам у него есть такая
function If there is no target it is eliminated in the air itself
функция Если цели нету он сам в воздухе
the same way they
ликвидируется так же само они его
checked it it flew out flew to the point and they
проверили он вылетел летел в точку и они
just eliminated it from it it just
его просто ликвидировали от него просто
went like this dawn
пошло как бы этот зари
And this hazelnut tree didn't damage anything at all
А этот орешник ничего не повредил вообще
no it just like what is this word
не Нет его просто как бы как это слово
called well how they checked it
называется ну как проверили просто его
Well how does it work like it is cut or
Ну как он работает вот как отре он или
not Well does it work or not that's
нерей Ну работает он или не работает вот
how you take there roughly speaking this fuse
как берёшь там грубо говоря этот запал
does it work or not you check it the
работает ли он или нет проверяешь его
same way they decided I think after
так же само они решили Я думаю я после
this hazelnut tree I thought that now the
этого орешника Думал что всё сейчас
West will be scared and that's it why it is
Запад испугается и всё так вот почему он
not afraid because it was somewhere in the air they
не боится потому что он где-то в воздухе
blew up the hazelnut tree and that's it of course no one
взорвали орешник и всё конечно его никто
will be afraid of it Well of course it is not afraid it was
не будет бояться Ну конечно не боится он
just eliminated in the air it did not
просто в воздухе его ликвидировали он не
arrive it was just a glow in the air
прилетел он просто в воздухе пошло
it arrived So why
зарево он долетел Так а зачем тогда это
did they do it then Yes they checked it  checked
делали Да его проверяли проверяли Просто
it just works is it working or not
он работае орей он или не работает
released checked well will it fly how far will
выпустили проверили Ну полетит насколько
it fly checked it well the radius as
он долетит проверили его ну радиус как
if and also will not check or will the
бы а также не проверят или долетит
hazel fly to America it would just fly
орешник до Америки просто долетел бы
somewhere over the Atlantic it was blown up or
где-то над атлантикой его взорвали или
there Yes it is clear it is possible to blow up well just
там Да понятно можно взорвать ну просто
well they are waiting for a video of the moment I am waiting for the moment that
ну ждут видео момента я жду момента что
America is washed as Zhirinovsky said
Америку у моет как Жириновский говорил
honestly such a person He talked a lot
честно такой человек Он много
talked a lot but
разговаривал много разговаривал но
got to the points from where he got it is
попадал в точки откуда он это брал
unknown in fact history
неизвестно на самом-то деле история
Did he die a natural death also the source is silent
Умер ли он своей смертью тоже умалчивает
I think that Zhirinovsky He was
исто Я думаю что Жириновский Он был
so smart that they helped him leave
настолько умный что Ему помогли уйти на
this world Well I think yes that's why I think I am
этот свет Ну я думаю да поэтому я думаю
waiting for this moment I am waiting for this
я жду этого момента я жду этого вот
really what he said everything people laughed
реально что он говорил всё люди смеялись
people thought ha-ha-ha there like some
люди думали ха-ха-ха там типа какой-то
comedian is performing there something Some kind of something
комик выступает там что-то Какое что-то
wants to prove in fact everything
хочет доказать на самом деле всё
comes true and people are in shock people are just
сбывается и люди в шоке люди только
starting to think That's how stupid people were
начинают думать Вот насколько люди тупы
before they ha as well as to God as well as to God they
раньше они ха как и Богу как и Богу
go to God do not pray believe I believe God
ходят Богу не молятся веришь Бога верю
war begins they begin bombing
война начинается бомбят начинают
baptize Save do you believe in God I do I
креститься Спаси веришь в Бога я да я
really believe in God now I'm waiting for when I
очень верю в Бога вот сейчас жду когда я
'll go I'm waiting for a vacation now on the fifth to
поеду Жду вот отпуска сейчас д пятого
go straight to church what what are you
поехать что что ты
Muslim not I'm Orthodox but
мусульманин не я православный а
Orthodox and you know the 10 commandments I'm
православный а 10 заповедей знаешь я
Orthodox
православный вот у
I understand but you know the
меня понял а 10 заповедей знаешь
10 commandments no I don't know the 10 commandments And in what way are
нет 10 заповедей не знаю А в чём тогда
you
ты
Orthodox then Well I'm Orthodox in that
православный Ну я православный том то
what I believe I have some kind of Faith
что я верю у меня есть Вера какая-то
Hope Well and what kind of faith exactly
Надежда Ну а какая какая именно вера в
what is your Faith I'm just wondering
чём твоя Вера Просто интересно я не шарю
I don't know anything about this Orthodoxy I have a lot of questions I
в этих Православия я много вопросов Я
won't talk about this You are
насчёт этого не буду говорить Вот ты
Orthodox not I'm not a believer at all I
православный не я не верующий вообще я
see you don't have a cross or anything
вижу нет у тебя ни крестика ничего У
I don't have a Cross I'm not 0 elephant you know what
меня нет Креста я не 0 слон знаешь что
it is Well Well I just well why should I
такое Ну вот Ну я просто ну зачем я
tell you a lot I just believe
много рассказывать я просто верю ную
0 what 90 elephant Yes this is a very
0 что 90 слон Да это молитва очень
strong prayer there are 90 prayers in one in one
сильная там 90 молитв в одно в одной
icon again 90 what 90 prayers in one
иконке ещё раз 90 что 90 молитв в одной
icon this is the most protected
иконке это самое самое защищённое что
of all and how does it
есть из всех а как оно
work Come on a lot of questions as if
работает Давай много вопросов как будто
you  somewhere
ты где-то
recorded Shala te sya
запис Шала те ся
let's talk normally again Well yeah No
давай нормально ещё поговорим Ну да Не
well how is that not a lot of questions I don't
ну как это не много вопросов я как бы не
want a few records there will be fewer questions
хочу мало запис меньше будет вопросов
just like well you're a normal person
просто типа ну ты нормальный человек
usually here with you we can normally
обычно тут с тобой можно нормально можем
exchange telegrams if I have
телеграма обменяться будет время у меня
free time we'll talk Write to you
свободное мы с тобой пообщаемся Напиши
Come on you write I'll take a screenshot And
те Давай ты напиши я скриншот сделаю А
write I'll look for him now at my
напиши я сейчас его буду искать у меня
number And I'll add you
по номеру А я тея добавлю
broke down in short I see the
сорвался короче проню
guy is a believer Akhma America he will
пацан верующий ахма Америку он будет
spread like
разносить лайк
t and send this video to all the famous letter on
т и скиньте це видео всм знам пись на
my Instagram I don't know why this is for you For
мий Instagram Я не знаю для чого це тоб
some reason there to look at the office and for
Для чего то там дивитись на офес а для
you ond or three clicks and you try me
тебе онд або три клика а ти тримае мене
and I'll be kti Wow in me there are a bunch of fouls and
и я буду кти Вау в мене там Купа фолов и
in me there will be a cool mood to do
в мене буде класний настрий щоб робити
New cool video letter on my Instagram
Нови крут вдео пись на мий Instagram
popk Andriy that's
попк Андрий вот
it let me you  I'm
так давай я тебя
waiting L
чекаю L